[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This law says that if things can go wrong, they jolly well will!", "correct_answer": "Murphys Law", "incorrect_answers": ["Paddys Law", "O Tooles Law", "O Learys Law"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of dinosaur is Mama Dino, who appears in the movie Ice Age: Dawn of the Dinosaurs?", "correct_answer": "Tyrannosaurus", "incorrect_answers": ["Diplodocus", "Iguanodon", "Brontosaurus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Suleiman the Magnificent personally led Ottoman armies to conquer Belgrade, Rhodes, and most of Hungary.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Japanese agent of the evil S.P.E.C.T.R.E. organization leads James Bond to S.P.E.C.T.R.E.s headquarters in the movie You Only Live Twice?", "correct_answer": "Mr. Osato", "incorrect_answers": ["Mr. Nagumo", "Mr. Kirabuti", "Mr. Taheshita"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Big Ten Conference is a college athletic conference located in the northern United States.  It had this many members, as of the beginning of the new millennium.", "correct_answer": "11", "incorrect_answers": ["12", "9", "10"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what places does the nocturnal Aye-aye sleep during the daytime?", "correct_answer": "On trees", "incorrect_answers": ["On a branch, covering its body with a big leaf", "Hanging from a branch.", "In holes in the ground"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1919, Isaac Carasso established the first industrialized production of yogurt under the name Danone. What does Danone mean?", "correct_answer": "Little Daniel", "incorrect_answers": ["Every day", "Longevity", "Health"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Finish this line delivered by Forrest Gump when he was asking Jenny to marry him. I may not be smart man....", "correct_answer": "....but I know what love is.", "incorrect_answers": ["....but I know how to love.", "....but I will make a good husband.", "....but I will love you forever."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "You always get to see the same half of the moon.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who won the Academy Award for Best Actress in a Leading Role at the 81st Academy Awards 2009?", "correct_answer": "Kate Winslet", "incorrect_answers": ["Anne Hathaway", "Meryl Streep", "Angelina Jolie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the term for the state of temporary hibernation that Hummingbirds enter when food is not available?", "correct_answer": "Torpor", "incorrect_answers": ["Hush", "Stupor", "Stillness"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Claires obnoxious boyfriend in the hilarious movie Wedding Crashers?", "correct_answer": "Zach", "incorrect_answers": ["Chazz", "William", "Todd"]}]